accuratebackground.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Accurate Background

This Privacy Statement applies to accuratebackground.com (“Web Site”) and services owned and operated by Accurate Background.  Please carefully read our privacy policy to understand how we will treat the information you provide while visiting this Web Site and our service. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information. This policy may change from time to time. Please check the policy each time you use our Web Site for the most current information.

The TRUSTe certification covers only our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our Web Site www.accuratebackground.com and Accurate Background services. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Accurate Background.

In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal.  If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Accurate Background complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Accurate Background has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Accurate Backgrounds certification, please visit<http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

## Collection and Use of Information

### Tracking Technologies

We, and our partners, affiliates, or analytics and service providers, may employ tracking technologies such as cookies, beacons, scripts, and tags to analyze trends, to administer the Web Site, to track users’ movements around the Web Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

When you visit this Web Site, we may collect general Internet data, including your domain name, the web page from which you entered our Web Site, which of our web pages you visited, and how long you spend on each page. To collect this information, when you visit our Web Site, a “cookie” may be set on your computer. Cookies contain information that allows our web servers to recognize you whenever you visit. We utilize cookies to record session information, passwords, and the profile of subscribed clients at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our Web Site. We use the information we collect to study how this Web Site is used, so that we may improve and enhance your experience on our Web Site. We also use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our Web Site, although it is possible that some areas of our Web Site will not function properly if you do so. In particular, you may be required to accept cookies in order to complete certain actions on Accurate Background’s Web Site. We do not provide this information to outside parties other than for such reasons. No personal information is stored in cookies. If you would like to learn how to opt out of cookies using your browser settings, click [here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for cookies, click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118).

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information.

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Web Site or to display advertising based on your web browsing activity, use Local Storage (HTML5) to store content information and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

We partner with a third party to display advertising on our Web Site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this Web Site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)).

### Information You Provide

When you provide information through this Web Site, we use it only for the business transaction for which it was collected. Based on the nature of your transaction with us, you may provide to us certain personal information such as first and last name; home address, or other physical address; an email address (so we may contact you); a telephone number; a social security number; or certain other information, such as date of birth, employment information, schools attended, licenses held and other information as required to process your transaction collectively, (“PI”). In general, we will use the information collected from you for the purpose for which you provided such information. We will not release your PI to third parties except as necessary for us to process your transaction.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [customer_service@accuratebackground.com](mailto:customer_service@accuratebackground.com). If you do not want to receive e-mails from us in the future, please let us know by emailing, calling, or writing to us at the address below.

If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by emailing, calling, or writing to us at the address below.

### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as criminal searches and employment verification. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information:  
• as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process  
• when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,  
• if Accurate Background is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,  
• to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

### User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our newsletters or similar marketing services, you may correct, update, amend or delete/remove it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us by email, telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. Accurate Background will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you our marketing services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Protection of Your Information

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard the PI you provide to us. Our products and/or services online are transmitted through a secured socket layer (SSL) transmission. Further, we have security protocols and measures in place to protect the PI we maintain about you from unauthorized access or alteration. These measures include internal and external firewalls, physical security and technological security measures, and encryption of certain information (including login credentials). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web Site, you can contact us by emailing, calling, or writing to us at the address below.

### Policy Regarding Children

We define children as individuals under the age of 16. Our Web Site is not intended for the use of children and we do not intend to collect information about children through our Web Site.

### Personal Information Disclosure: United States or Overseas

Personal information submitted to Accurate Background for a background screening investigation may at times be transferred outside of the United States in order to perform the background investigation specifically when Accurate Background is attempting to verify your credentials or professional history during times you were in another country outside of the United States. All personal information will be transmitted and stored in a secure manner in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our Web Site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Accurate Background. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web Site includes Social Media Features such as the Share this button, Facebook Like button, or interactive mini-programs that run on our Web Site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Web Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Web Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Blog with Comments

Our Web Site offers publicly accessible blogs. You should be aware that any information you provide in this area may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us by using the contact information provided below. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials and other endorsements of satisfied customers on our Web Site. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us by using the contact information provided below.

### Changes to This Policy

Accurate Background, Inc. may revise or update this privacy policy on occasion to reflect changes to our practices. If we make any material changes we will provide notification through the Company’s Web Site prior to the change taking effect. You should refer back to this page for the latest information and the effective date of any changes.

### Information Related to Data Collected through Accurate Background’s Services

Accurate Background collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes.

### Choice

We collect information for our Clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly.

### Service Provider, Sub-Processors/Onward Transfer

Accurate Background may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients

### Access to Data Controlled by our Clients

Accurate Background has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Accurate Backgrounds Client (the data controller). If the Client requests Accurate Background to remove the data related to our marketing services and/or newsletters, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

### Data Retention

Accurate Background will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Accurate Background will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Contact Us:

Compliance Director  
Accurate Background  
7515 Irvine Center Drive  
Irvine, CA 92618  
800.784.3911  

**Effective Date:**  November 24, 2015

## Terms of Use

Welcome to our accuratebackground.com. If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Accurate Background’s relationship with you in relation to this website.

The term ‘Accurate Background’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is 7515 Irvine Center Drive, Irvine, CA 92618. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.

The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

  * The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
  * Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.
  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
  * This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
  * All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.
  * Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offense.
  * From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
  * You may not create a link to this website from another website or document without Accurate Background’s prior written consent.
  * Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of the State of California.
